Love... it's a balancing act
Playing It Cool is a comedy, romance film directed by Justin Reardon.
A young man meets and instantly falls in love with an engaged woman.
Narrator, played by Chris Evans.
Her, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Scott, played by Topher Grace.
Mallory, played by Aubrey Plaza.
Samson, played by Luke Wilson.
Lyle, played by Martin Starr.
Playing It Cool is a 2014 American romantic comedy film directed by
Justin Reardon and written by Chris Shafer and Paul Vicknair.
The film stars Chris Evans and Michelle Monaghan.
The film was released on video on demand on March 31, 2015 before a
limited release on May 8, 2015 by Vertical Entertainment.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of screenwriter, romcom, romance, love, friends.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.